It's been two years since the War of the Best in Marineford.
Scattered across the world, Luffy and his crew underwent special training to prepare for the trials ahead.
Now, they return to the Sabahodi Archipelago and move forward to the next stage of their journey, the New World.
Wow.
Oh, yeah? Nobody else has shown up?
How about you check that poster again? If your bounty is under 70 million, then we don't want you.
So why don't you take your weak ass back to Pirate Daycare?
Too late.
I'm only gonna say this once.
You can take your offer and shove it, cause I'm way out of your league.
Special Attack Green Star?
Devil!
Hey there, beautiful. Can I buy you a drink?
Ahem.
Come on, babies!
Yeah!
I'll lift you down to my balls!
I hope not! Thanks for the ride and say hi to Eva, but go away!
Brooke is holding a concert, and the Straw Hats are looking for new recruits?
Goodness, I've been gone for too long.
I'm sorry to keep you waiting, Sonny. We'll be sailing off soon.
Ugh!
Ugh…
Oops.
Didn't see you there.
Sorry about that.
See ya!
Get back here!
An explosive situation. Luffy vs. Fake Luffy.
Not good.
There in the distance is Saba Odi Archipelago.
Forgive me, Luffy, but we will have to say our goodbyes here.
We cannot let anyone discover the nature of our relationship.
I've prepared a disguise for you.
Are you kidding? I can't pull that look off.
Perhaps. But I would still feel more at ease if you took it.
Alright.
You must be careful. Keep your face hidden at all times.
The world may believe you've been dead these last two years,
but that won't stop anyone from recognizing you the first time you get into trouble.
So if you ever want to set sail again, you'll take my advice to heart.
Thanks. I'll try.
You're welcome. Now, for supplies, I've loaded your backpack with 50 changes of clothes, 1,000 lunches, handkerchiefs, and tissues.
You'll also find three years worth of water, snacks, and bug bite ointment.
There's also five years worth of towels, toothbrushes, plenty of soaps, hand creams, and lots of silverware.
That is entirely too much!
Well, I hope you can find all your friends.
Thanks again for getting me here and all the other stuff.
We were more than happy to help you.
Your most difficult trials may still be ahead of you. I hear that Saba Odi has become a den of crime.
Mm-hmm. And because of that, the Navy has been keeping a tight watch over the goings-on there as of late, my boy.
So be sure to take extra care!
Right.
If you ever need assistance, the full force of the Kuja pirates will come rushing to your aid at a moment's notice.
Please don't hesitate to call on us.
Also, would you be willing to do me a favor?
Yeah, maybe. As long as it's not getting married.
No, no. All I ask is that when you leave, you do so without saying farewell.
That all? I've never said that to anyone before, so sure.
Besides, I want to see you again.
All right, I'm out of here!
You take care!
Oh, my! He wants to see me again! That's practically a proposal!
No, it's not!
Hancock told me I gotta stay out of trouble and lay low. I don't wanna fight this guy.
Hey, dummy! Did you run into me on purpose?
Oh, no! He's gonna kill that poor guy!
You're kidding me! You're saying this swordsman who barely knows left from right got here first?
Well, what do you know? Maybe he learned how to read a map while he was training.
After him came Frankie about ten days ago now, but he headed back out to go see if your ship was doing all right.
I hope that means the Sunny is in good shape.
Of course. There isn't a single scratch on it. We finished the coding, too.
That's good to hear.
Just make sure you give credit where credit's due.
Even if he don't, there's no shame in a wound of honor.
It's time for some R&R!
Who knew you'd be so dedicated to the cause?
Your stubbornness came in handy.
You mean my looks?
Don't mention it. I owe you one anyway.
Come rain or shine, it changed nothing.
Dangerous pirates from all over came to take that ship.
Didn't matter how bad I was hurt. I defended it day after day.
Cause I knew all these bruises would be worth it.
You're so amazing, sir!
Pirates messed you up? Come on, what's the real story here, Duval?
Don't be impatient. I'm trying to build up the suspense here, you know.
You see, what happened was the Navy showed up.
The third member of your crew to arrive was Nami.
Nami!
That's great, is she still here?
She decided to kill time by getting some shopping done.
Come on, don't you want to hear the rest of my story?
Nami shopping, Nami shopping, Nami shopping.
The fourth one to arrive was Usopp three days ago, who also went into town, followed by Chopper, who showed up yesterday.
Brooks made it too. He's putting on a concert for the Islanders today.
No way. Well, I'll be damned.
You're the last to stop by, which makes seven in total.
Not that I expected any less, but almost the entire crew has made it back in good time.
That's right. Only Niko, Robin, and Luffy remain.
Getting to this island in the first place is a difficult task for any crew to accomplish.
And yet, you've made it twice. What can I say? You must be eager to see each other again.
Yeah. And by the way, I still can't believe you trained Luffy while we were gone.
He must be crazy strong now.
He's been on his own these last six months. I can't wait to see how his skills have developed.
Now that you... mention it...
I can't wait to see how Nami's developed, if you know what I'm saying!
I should have expected that.
Hey, are you alright?
I endured two years of arduous training, just like everybody else.
I'm more resilient than ever. Showing no sign of seduction.
You have to wipe your nose before anyone believes that!
Run!
Those lousy thugs! Always fighting!
I kinda thought the pirates were gonna settle down once Whitebeard died.
Man, I wish. Instead, they're coming in from all over the place.
They're overrun with them! Our entire island is a lawless mess!
It's dangerous. I had no idea things were so bad.
Have you learned your lesson?
It may look like Blackbeard Kid and Drake are running things in the New World, but look again!
Now it's only a matter of time until we follow, I mean, beat them at their own game!
Yeah!
It could be. The rumors are true, just like I thought.
The Navy didn't kill them two years ago. They didn't even capture them.
And now they're back on the island, ready to start trouble again.
Right. And ever since they got back here, they've become the most powerful pirate group on the island, too.
The Straw Hats! They're here!
Really? Is it Nami? Rusa?
No! It's too soon!
That's Pirate Hunter Zorro. He's got a 120 million berry bounty!
And Blackfoot Sanji's with him. His bounty's up to 77 million!
But that's nothing when you consider that Nico Robin theirs had a bounty since she was eight.
She's worth 80 million!
Then there's their pet. Their cotton candy lover, Tony Tony Chopper. 50 berry bounty!
Pocket change!
Let me through! Is Luffy there? Hey, move! You're blocking my view!
This is the perfect opportunity for us!
Let's take him!
Wait! Why are you holding us back, Captain?
If we cause trouble with them, there's nothing that'll stop Straw Hat Luffy from coming after our heads.
We don't need that kind of fight barreling down on us, especially not right before we go to the New World.
Hey! Zorro! Sanji! Stop! Robin, wait for me!
Huh? I think that raccoon's trying to talk to us.
Huh? Are you listening to yourself, man? Everybody knows raccoons can't talk.
Are you sure?
I can't believe you were the first one to make it here, Zorro! I thought you'd get lost for sure!
And Sanji, Robin, I'm glad to see you made it safe and sound!
See what I tell you?
I don't know what that's supposed to be, but it could spell big trouble for us if we're not careful. Let's go!
Hey! Slow down! Don't leave me to hide, you guys!
Our target, Nico Robin, has devil fruit powers. We can't afford to fight someone like her alone. Our only hope is to try and catch her off guard.
It's been a while. Surely the others have made it back by now.
I can't wait for Nami and Robin to get here so they can try my new and improved recipes!
But before they can, I'll have to make sure the Sunny's kitchen is up to my standards.
I better stop getting full of ingredients!
Was that... Sanji?
So what are you gonna say for yourself? You can't tell me you didn't know who I was when you crashed into me!
Why do it? Were you just trying to make a fool out of me? Cause if so, I don't like being shown up in public.
After all, I have a reputation and a 400 million buried bounty to uphold.
But you can make it up to me by kneeling. Beg for your life and I might feel generous.
You can make it up to me by kneeling.
Come on. Just apologize already! Don't you have something you want to live for?
Heh. Well, kid, whatcha thinking? You screwed up and now it's time to pay. So speak up!
Please, take a look at that brat. Obviously you scared him silent, Captain!
I can't blame the kid. After that guy with the schnoz and that chick with the long hair picked a fight with us, we're in a worse mood than usual.
Now if you don't want to be our personal punching bag, you'd best ask forgiveness.
Kneel, get down in the dirt! Forget your pride. Otherwise you're gonna end up throwing your life away over some small mistake.
After all, our Captain's trigger figure can be a little twitchy.
Come on, kid. Just do it! You shouldn't mess around with Straw Hat Luffy!
You're gonna die if you don't do what he says!
Alright, look. I'm sorry. I got somewhere to be.
What's wrong with you?
Bad move. Say goodbye, punk.
Gangster dog!
Aeah!
Cucking
What happened?
Hey, that guy, did he do something?
Guess Hancock was right.
Maybe I do need to wear that thing.
Hey, guys!
What's the matter?
Come on, talk to me!
I thought you'd be more excited to see me,
but you're acting weird.
From the looks of things,
you've all changed a lot over these last two years.
But, I mean, we're still friends,
so why are you ignoring me?
You, man, is not leaving.
Oh, you must be shy
because of how much I've changed, too.
And if you ask me,
that furball knows a little too much
about us straw hats, if you know what I mean.
Yeah, I do.
You gotta wonder why that is.
Maybe we can find the answer here.
Oh, no, it can't be.
Huh?
That's the real deal,
cotton candy-loving Tony Tony Chopper.
The pet's coming home.
So we all look a little different than we used to.
Who cares?
He must have been abandoned on this island
when they died,
and he's been living in the wild ever since.
And now he's following us around
because he thinks his masters have finally come back for him.
We should ditch the mutt and take him instead.
If we have their real pet,
no one will ever doubt we're the straw hats again.
Sounds good.
What's he eat?
Probably cotton candy.
We ain't got none of that.
Yes, we don't need you no more.
Come here, boy.
You hungry?
Yum, right?
You're kind of freaking me out.
Now!
Robin!
Hey!
Stop!
Come back!
Who were those creeps?
Oh, no!
This is a real emergency!
What are we gonna do now?
I guess we should tell Captain Luffy, right?
Maybe he knows how to handle this mess.
Wait!
I didn't know Luffy was back on the island already!
You're right.
And he'll have new recruits by now.
That's great!
With the extra might,
we'll save Robin for sure!
Let's go get our friend back!
Calling from Sabaoni!
We've secured Nico Robin!
We've also caught some fox thing
that won't stop biting her head!
I shouldn't be worried if Frankie is so fired up.
The Sunny will be just fine
until I make my way back with all of the, uh...
Fever Sabaoni!
Gotta stay focused, Sanji.
Your first priority is finding the best ingredients you can
for the crew's meals.
Oh, boy!
Beautiful!
I've been needing a lady just like you in my life!
And once the pantry is stocked,
I'll make something really special
for both Robin and Nami.
The only problem is...
nothing in this market is really standing out.
What should I do?
Gotcha!
That's a tough spot,
but your best bet is the shop on the beach
in Grow 42.
Thank you!
I'll head there now!
Yo!
Fisherman, you in?
I'm looking for some good stock at a low price!
Huh?
Is the place...
Hey, you run this shack!
What's the matter?
It's something awful!
That green-haired man's gone!
Aw, crap.
All right, old man, spill it.
I can't believe this has happened to me!
Well, you see...
Uh...
Hey, Gramps.
Huh?
I was looking to do some fishing.
No offense, young man,
but I wouldn't exactly peg you as the fishing type.
Normally, you'd be right.
I'm supposed to be meeting some friends on this island,
but they haven't made it yet.
So I'm bored out of my skull.
So I need something to keep me entertained while I wait.
You think you can help me out or not?
Sure!
I'll finish getting everything we need ready
and then meet you on my boat right over there.
And that's all I said to him.
To be clear,
did this guy have three swords
and a belly warmer?
Yes, he did.
And he had a deep scar on his eye, too.
How'd you know?
Scars knew.
Is this him?
Yeah!
He said he'd been waiting on some friends to show.
That must be you.
Well, I wouldn't go that far.
You see,
I told him to wait on my fishing boat
while I was getting ready,
and I pointed right at the thing.
But when I came outside,
he'd made a huge mistake!
No!
Young man!
You've got it wrong!
You're on a pirate ship!
No, men!
It's time we set sail for the new world
we've been dreaming of!
The wait is over!
Come on, please!
You have to wake up!
You're not on the pirate ship!
Since they went underwater,
I guess they were headed to Fishman Island.
That idiot!
Should have known him showing up here first
was too good to be true.
Wouldn't be Zoro
if he didn't get lost somewhere.
Aren't you worried at all?
They might kill him on that ship!
It's fine.
Don't get worked up.
This is pretty standard fare, actually.
Better than usual,
even since we know where he's going for once.
Now, would you mind selling me some fish already?
I don't think you understand.
Whoa!
See that?
Huh?
Look at the waves!
Something's coming up!
But what?
It must be huge!
That's a galleon ship!
He must have had poor coating
and was crushed under the water pressure!
No, it has to be the work of Sea Kings!
But it looks like it's been cut in half!
Like someone attacked it!
No way!
Just think for a second!
Who in the world could do that?
Damn you!
Tell me why!
How could you just ruin our dreams
of reaching the new world like this?
Call it a twist of fate!
That's what brought this plague upon your ship!
And there's no one for you to blame but yourselves!
Are you kidding me?
Who the heck is that guy?
Oh great, back already!
And he's still a pain in the ass!
That...
Wasn't my ride!
One by one, the Straw Hats reunite
as they prepare to depart for the new world
as soon as possible.
However, Sintomaru and the Navy
have yet again amassed a team of pacifistas
threatening to repeat the same tragedy
that drove the crew from Sabaori two years ago.
On the next, One Piece!
The Navy has set out!
The Straw Hat's in danger!
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!